Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series
1880-1920
University Archives
Princeton University. Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections
Princeton University. Library. Special Collections
AC317
148 boxes
Consists of approximately 2,180 glass plate negatives and prints. Topics most heavily represented within the collection include Princeton University buildings and grounds, and athletics.
Scope and Contents
Consists of approximately 3500 glass plate negatives and prints containing images of Princeton University, primarily of the campus and buildings
Arrangement
All descriptive information was transcribed from material enclosures. The source of these descriptions is unknown. Due to the unreliability of these transcribed descriptions, no extensive arrangement of the materials has been undertaken. In order to help facilitate search, some descriptions have been grouped by common theme.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the glass-plate negatives is restricted due to their fragility. Where prints of the negatives are present, the prints are open for research use. Though digitization may not be possible for every negative, researchers may make requests to digitize material according to Mudd Library's policy on digitization of photographs
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection has been assembled through multiple accessions
Appraisal
Appraisal information was not recorded at time of accessioning
Education, Higher.; Photographs.; Princeton University. Buildings; Princeton University. Photographs.
- Athletics, 1881-1938; 51 boxes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access to the glass-plate negatives is restricted due to their fragility. Where prints of the negatives are present, the prints are open for research use. Though digitization may not be possible for every negative, researchers may make requests to digitize material according to Mudd Library's policy on digitization of photographs
  Scope and Contents
  Glass plates within this series show peoples and events related to Princeton University athletics.
  Some images lack description and may be unrelated.
  Arrangement
  No arrangement action taken at the time of processing.
  - Individual Athletes, 1900; 12 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images and portratits of Princeton University athletes and coaches.
    - P.U. sports, John Dwight?, Undated; 1 box (Box 62)
      Plate number: 1209
    - Bill Coanie, Princetonian and coach, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1215
    - DeWitt with hammer, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1217
    - Dan Horton, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1218
    - Roper, Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - Dewitt, Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - Stur McClur, Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - Dewitt, poor ball O.K., Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - P. Waller, '05 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 79)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 81, Box 82)
    - Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1259-1266
    - Rulon-Miller: football uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1267
    - Craig: football uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1268
    - Palmer: track & field uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1269
    - Hutchinson: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1270
    - Sides: baseball uniform (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1271
    - Parry: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1272
    - R. McClair: football uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1273
    - Christie: track & field uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1274
    - Throckmorton: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1275
    - Hutchings holding hat (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1276
    - Craig: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1277
    - Newcomb: baseball uniform (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1278
    - Davis: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1279
    - Walker: baseball uniform (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1280
    - Brown: football uniform (P.U.), 1900; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1281
    - Chapman: baseball uniform (catcher) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1282
    - Chapman: baseball uniform (1st base) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1283
    - E. Dillon: football uniform (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1284
    - McCormick: football uniform (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1285
    - Vaughn: baseball uniform (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1286
    - Phiffer: football uniform (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1287
    - Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1288-1290
    - Football player (letter sweater) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1291
    - Football player (with helmet), Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1292
    - Football player, Undated; 1 box (Box 83)
      Plate number: 1293
    - Football player (P.U.), Undated; 3 boxes (Box 83, Box 84, Box 85)
      Plate number: 1294-1298, 1301-1302, 1305, 1308-1318, 1320-13223, 1325-1330, 1333-1335, 1337-1348, 1355-1360
    - Football player '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1299
    - Football player '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1300
    - Football player, Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1303
    - Football player (Brown & Nichols sweaters) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1304
    - Football player, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 84, Box 85)
      Plate number: 1306-1307, 1349-1350
    - 4 Football players (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1319
    - Football player (P.A. on vest) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 84)
      Plate number: 1324
    - Football player (with helmet) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1331
    - Football player (letter sweater) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1332, 1336
    - Clarke Coach of P.U. baseball team, Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1351
    - Robinson James athletic trainer P.U., Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1352-1354
    - Black: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1361
    - Herring Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1362
    - Herring Football player (w. letter) (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1363
    - Hart: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1364
    - Herman: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1365
    - Munn: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 85)
      Plate number: 1366
    - Martin: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1367
    - McCormick: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1368
    - Monroe: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1369
    - Gordon: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1370
    - Brown: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1371
    - Edward, Poe, Balliat (?) 3 Football players (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1372
    - Beardsley: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1373
    - Beardsley: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1374
    - McClane: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1375
    - Stumbird: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1376
    - Moose: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1377
    - Burke: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1378
    - Sheffield: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1379
    - Pierson: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1380
    - Mattis: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1381
    - Duncan: Football player (P.U.) '01, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1382
    - Butterscotch: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1383
    - McCord: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1384
    - Bookum: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1385
    - Daub: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1386
    - Hoagland: Football player (P.U.) '06 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1387
    - Tibbletts: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1388
    - Cass: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1389
    - Stannard: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1390
    - Stannard: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1391
    - Harlon: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1392
    - Munn: Football player (P.U.) '05 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1393
    - Munn: Football player (P.U.) '05 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1394
    - Couney: Football player (captain) (P.U.) '05 P.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1395
    - Brazier: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1396
    - Tooker: Football player (letter sweater) (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1397
    - Waller: Football player (letter sweater) (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1398
    - O'Brien: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1399
    - Harlon: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1400
    - Rafferty: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1401
    - Dana: Football player (P.U.) '00, Undated; 1 box (Box 86)
      Plate number: 1402
    - Stannard: Football player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1403
    - Williamson: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1404
    - Daub: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1405
    - Dillon, H.: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1406
    - McClean: Baseball Payer (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1407
    - Cooney: Baseball Payer (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1408
    - Harlon: Baseball Payer (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1409
    - Watkins: Baseball Payer (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1410
    - Jones: Baseball Payer (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1411
    - Roper: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1412
    - Kafer: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1413
    - Hutchings: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1414
    - Doyle, L.: Baseball player (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1415
    - Wister: Football player (P.U.) '06 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1416
    - Byram: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1417
    - Suter:: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1418
    - Harrison: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1419
    - McClane: Football player (P.U.) '99 J.B., Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1420
    - Paulmeirs: Baseball player (P.U.) '94, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1421
    - Holt: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1422
    - Hillebrand: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1423
    - Clark: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1424
    - Hersing: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1425
    - Underhill: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1426
    - Fisher: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1427
    - Musuipt: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1428
    - Head, Ruther (Coach?) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1429
    - McClure, S.: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1430
    - Carouthers: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1431
    - Bard: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1432
    - Simons: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1433
    - Hardy: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1434
    - Vaugh: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1435
    - Walker, P.: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1436
    - Phillips: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1437
    - Ripley, Bait: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 87)
      Plate number: 1438
    - Bannard: Football (Coach?) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1439
    - Lee: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1440
    - Steinwinder: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1441
    - Robinson: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1442
    - Longdon: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1443
    - Wright: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1444
    - Davis: Football player (letter sweater) (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1445
    - Meeir: Football player (P.U.) '00, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1446
    - Bayless: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1447
    - McCord: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1448
    - Little: Football player (P.U.) '00, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1449
    - Chapman: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1450
    - Losey: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1451
    - Dewitt: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1452
    - Roper: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1453
    - Doc: Baseball Trainer (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1454
    - Heinager: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1455
    - Hale: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1456
    - Burke: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1457
    - Watkins: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1458
    - Green: Baseball player (P.U.) '00, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1459
    - Watkins & Burke: Baseball (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1460
    - Brown: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1461
    - Scott: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1462
    - Hutchings: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1463
    - Peirson: Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1464
    - Jarvis: Track (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1465
    - Hutchinson: Track (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1466
    - Willis: Track (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1467
    - Reiter: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1468
    - Loyd (sic): Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1469
    - Hodyman: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1470
    - Tenney: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1471
    - Wister: Baseball player (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1472
    - Dillon: Baseball player (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1473
    - Henry: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 88)
      Plate number: 1474
    - Vaugh: Baseball player (P.U.) '07, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1475
    - Robinson, James: Athletic trainer (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1476
    - Levick: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1477
    - Bush: Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1478
    - Dugro: Football player (P.U.) '02, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1479
    - Frier: Football player (P.U.) '05, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1480
    - Doyle: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1481
    - Bard: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1482
    - Doyle: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1483
    - Harlon: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1484
    - Dillon: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1485
    - Sides: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1486
    - Reid: Baseball player (captain) (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1487
    - Newcomb: Baseball player (P.U.) '06, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1488
    - Princeton Prep School football, unidentified player, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1489-1491
    - Princeton Prep School baseball, unidentified player, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1492
    - Princeton U. - 3 Baseball players, Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1493
    - Baseball player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1494-1495
    - Football player (P.U.), Undated; 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1496-1498
  - Baseball, 1892-1936; 14 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Baseball team.
    - Baseball, shows players on field and good view of grandstand and bleachers, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      No paper print
      Plate number: 252
    - Baseball, bleachers scene, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 253-254
    - Baseball, freshman-sophmore game, bleachers scene, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 255-261
    - Baseball team, 1905, 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 262
    - Baseball team, no date, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 263-272
    - Baseball team, 1932-33, 1932-1933; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 273
    - Baseball team, 1935, 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 274
    - Baseball team, 1936, 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 275
    - Sophmore-Freshman baseball game, bleacher crowd, Undated; 1 box (Box 19)
      Plate number: 339-340
    - Baseball team, 1896, 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 362
    - Baseball team, 1920, 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 363
    - Baseball team, Undated; 1 box (Box 22)
      Plate number: 364
    - A close play at first in the Dartmouth baseball game, 1920, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 162
      Plate number: 694
    - Panorama of University field during baseball game in spring of 1920, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 163
      Plate number: 695
    - Baseball practice in University field, 1920, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 164
      Plate number: 696
    - A run coming in, 1919 baseball session, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1041
      Plate number: 1047
    - Close play at first base, 1919, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1040
      Plate number: 1046
    - 16-0 scoreboard in Princeton Harvard game, 1918, 1 box (Box 55)
      Original sleeve No. 1042
      Plate number: 1048
    - Old grand stand at University field during a spring game, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1043
      Plate number: 1049
    - Bill Kirkland, Pitcher, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1046
      Plate number: 1052
    - Safe at first in baseball game, 1919, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1044
      Plate number: 1050
    - Captain Bade of baseball team at bat, 1919, 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1098
      Plate number: 1097
    - Clowe play at first in Princeton baseball game, Undated; 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1145
      Plate number: 1124
    - Yale-Princeton baseball, Undated; 1 box (Box 63)
      Plate number: 1216
    - Athletics, baseball, Jesse Holt, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1224
    - Athletics, baseball with Pennsylvania, captains of teams and umpires, crowd in bleachers, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1225
    - Atheletics, baseball in action shot, 1915?, circa 1915; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1226
    - Athletics, baseball, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1228
    - 1892 Princeton baseball team, circa 1892; 1 box (Box 91)
    - Baseball game, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
      8x10
    - Princeton University 1903 baseball individuals, 1 box (Box 80)
    - Princeton University 1904 baseball individuals, 1 box (Box 80)
    - Princeton University 1905 baseball individuals, 1 box (Box 80)
  - Basketball, 1914-1938; 9 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Basketball team.
    - Jim Hynson, captain of 1920 basketball team, circa 1920; 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 139
      Plate number: 670
    - 1918-19 basketball squad of Princeton, 1918-1919; 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 140
      Plate number: 671
    - 1919-1920 basketball squad, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 141
      Plate number: 672
    - 1919-1920 basketball squad of Princeton, 1 box (Box 33)
      Original sleeve No. 142
      Plate number: 673
    - Freshman basketball team of 1923, 1 box (Box 35)
      Original sleeve No. 155
      Plate number: 687
    - 1918 varsity basketball team, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1058
      Plate number: 1064
    - Athletics, basketball team, 1914-15, Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1227
    - Athletics, basketball, 2 players, F. Glick, J.E. Butterworthy, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1229
    - Men's basketball, 1936-1938, 1 box (Box 92)
    - Men's basketball, 1929-1931, 1 box (Box 92)
    - Men's basketball, 1931 state champs, 1 box (Box 92)
    - Women's basketball team, Princeton H.S., 1921-1922, 1 box (Box 93)
    - Early basketball game, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Early basketball, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Early basketball, Undated; 1 box (Box 103)
      5x7
  - Boxing, 1914-1919; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture Princeton University Boxing.
    - Freshman required exercise in the gym, (Boxing), winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 113
      Plate number: 644
    - Athletics, boxing in Whig Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 64)
      Plate number: 1230
    - "Spider" Kelly coaching boxing class, Princeton U., Dec. 1914, 1 box (Box 89)
      Plate number: 1499
  - Crew, 1913-1920; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries capture the Princeton University Rowing team.